<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ServerManagerConfiguration>
  <ProxyGroup name="sources">
      <SourceProxy class="vtkPeanoExplorer"
                   label="Peano Explorer"
                   name="GenericClip">
        <Documentation long_help="Clip with an implicit plane, sphere or with scalars. Clipping does not reduce the dimensionality of the data set.  This output data type of this filter is always an unstructured grid."
                       short_help="Clip with an implicit plane, sphere or with scalars.">
                       The Generic Clip filter cuts away a portion of the input
                       data set using a plane, a sphere, a box, or a scalar
                       value. The menu in the Clip Function portion of the
                       interface allows the user to select which implicit
                       function to use or whether to clip using a scalar value.
                       Making this selection loads the appropriate user
                       interface. For the implicit functions, the appropriate 3D
                       widget (plane, sphere, or box) is also displayed. The use
                       of these 3D widgets, including their user interface
                       components, is discussed in section 7.4. If an implicit
                       function is selected, the clip filter returns that portion
                       of the input data set that lies inside the function. If
                       Scalars is selected, then the user must specify a scalar
                       array to clip according to. The clip filter will return
                       the portions of the data set whose value in the selected
                       Scalars array is larger than the Clip value. Regardless of
                       the selection from the Clip Function menu, if the Inside
                       Out option is checked, the opposite portions of the data
                       set will be returned. This filter operates on all types of
                       data sets, and it returns unstructured grid data on output.
        </Documentation>
        <ProxyProperty command="SetBoxFunction"
                       label="Clip Type"
                       name="ClipFunction">
          <ProxyGroupDomain name="groups">
            <Group name="implicit_functions" />
          </ProxyGroupDomain>
          <ProxyListDomain name="proxy_list">
            <Proxy group="implicit_functions"
                   name="Box" />
          </ProxyListDomain>
          <Documentation>Set the parameters of the clip function.</Documentation>
        </ProxyProperty>
        <DoubleVectorProperty information_only="1"
                              name="InputBounds">
          <BoundsDomain name="bounds">
            <RequiredProperties>
              <Property function="Input"
                        name="Input" />
            </RequiredProperties>
          </BoundsDomain>
        </DoubleVectorProperty>
        <Hints>
          <Visibility replace_input="2" />
        </Hints>
        <!-- End GenericClip -->
      </SourceProxy>
  </ProxyGroup>
</ServerManagerConfiguration>
